Harvard University, Graduate School of Design. The GSD History Collection, Administrative Affairs: An Inventory
Harvard University, Graduate School of Design. The GSD History Collection, Administrative Affairs: An Inventory
- Series D: Harvard University GSD, Administrative Affairs: Events, / Date(s): 1969-1986 (bulk) -- 1966-2000 (inclusive); D000; / Quantity: 6 boxes / Dimensions: 6 linear ft. / Medium: varies / Support: varies
  - Subseries DB: Events -- Special Events (Demonstrations, Celebrations, Anniversaries) -- Harvard Anniversary, / Date(s): 1986; Folder: DB136; / Quantity: 3 items / Dimensions: 15" x 7" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Leaflet with cover and back cover with drawings of Robinson Hall and Gund Hall. Text invites alumni to generate "birthday greetings" for the GSD and to send in their submissions for an exhibition to be held at the GSD on occasion of the 50th Anniversary.
  - Subseries DB: Events -- Special Events (Demonstrations, Celebrations, Anniversaries) -- Harvard Anniversary, / Date(s): 1986; Folder: DB137; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 14" x 11" / Medium: photostats / Support: paper
    Note: Photostats of Gund Hall (section) and Robinson Hall (elevation) used in invitation included in DB136.
  - Subseries DB: Events -- Special Events (Demonstrations, Celebrations, Anniversaries) -- Harvard Anniversary, / Date(s): 1986; Box: DB138; / Quantity: 40 items / Dimensions: 14" x 11" / Medium: mixed media / Support: paper; cardboard
    Note: Box with Alumni Anniversary Drawings. This project was initiated by the GSD Alumni Council to celebrate the 50th anniversary of the school. Both Robinson Hall and Gund Hall are incorporated in the drawings in some way.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures and Symposia, / Date(s): 1978-2000 (inclusive); Subseries: DC000; / Quantity: 65 folders / Dimensions: 2-1/2 linear ft. / Medium: print; typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Subseries DC: Events - Conferences, Lectures and Symposia is comprised of 65 folders (GSD History - Administrative. Boxes 14, 15 and 16) and contains papers related to general conferences and lectures, as well as major symposia such as the 100th Anniversary of Landscape Architecture at Harvard.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1979-1980; Folder: DC001; / Quantity: 41 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: mimeograph / Support: paper
    Note: Several copies of GSD Calendar: This Week, for academic calendar year 1979-1980 (weekly).
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1980-1983; Folder: DC002; / Quantity: 18 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: GSD Calendar, 1980-1983 (monthly).
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1984-1985; Folder: DC003; / Quantity: 13 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: GSD Calendar, 1984-1985 (monthly).
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1978-1982; Folder: DC004; / Quantity: 4 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
    Note: List of lecturers, 1978-1982.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1978-1982; Folder: DC005; / Quantity: 47 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript; newsprint / Support: paper
    Note: Gund Lectures and Exhibitions, 1978-1979 (Publicity. Includes press releases and clippings.
    Location of associated materials: See also DC006.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1978-1982; Folder: DC006; / Quantity: 17 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript; newsprint / Support: paper
    Note: Continuation of Gund Lectures and Exhibitions, 1978-1979 (Publicity. Includes press releases and clippings.
    Location of associated materials: See also DC005.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1976; Folder: DC007; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 9" x 7" / Medium: typescript; newsprint / Support: paper
    Note: Press release and clippings on Colloquium held at the GSD on Urban Development.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1981; Folder: DC008; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 12" x 9" / Medium: typescript; newsprint / Support: paper
    Note: Press release, clippings, brochure and schedule for Knoll Symposium, held at the GSD, 1981. Folder handed out by Knoll includes portrait of Marcel Breuer.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1982; Folder: DC009; / Quantity: 27 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Typescript "Response to the Exhibition" related to Hitchcock and Johnson's 1932 exhibition at MoMA. Also includes correspondence related to International Style in Perspective conference at GSD and attendee listings.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1982; Folder: DC010; / Quantity: 47 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Records related to a Meeting on Design Education at the GSD in 1982. Sponsored by the Association of Collegiate Schools of Architecture and the National Design Committee of the AIA.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1984; Folder: DC011; / Quantity: 10 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript; photographs / Support: paper; photographic paper
    Note: Clippings, photographic contact sheets and photographs related to the GSD's International Training Program attended by officials of the Korean Land Development Corporation.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1982; Folder: DC012; / Quantity: 17 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript; photographs / Support: paper; photographic paper
    Note: Clippings, photographic contact sheets and photographs related to the Skowhegan Charette.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1983; Folder: DC013; / Quantity: 14 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript; print / Support: paper
    Note: Brochure / flyer and press release related to the Superfund Conference to be held at the GSD to discuus the "Massachusetts Oil & Hazardous Materials Release Prevention and Response Act".
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1991; Folder: DC014; / Quantity: 40 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 5-1/2" x 8-1/2" / Medium: typescript; print / Support: paper
    Note: Correspondence and outlines exchanged among alumni and GSD's external relations director in relation to GSD Greater Boston Focus Group. Also includes brochure of The Boston Bash, a "celebration and exploration of design in Boston by GSD alumni/ae and faculty", 1991.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1984; Folder: DC015; / Quantity: 40 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript; print / Support: paper
    Note: Steering committee meetings, clippings and afterthoughts related to The Boston Conference: A City and Its Future, 1984. Includes The Boston Globe "The Livable City" issue, inspired in the conference held at Quincy Market and supported by a grant from the National Endowment for the Arts and sponsored by several academic institution of Massachusetts (among them, Harvard University).
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1985-1986; Folder: DC016; / Quantity: 40 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript; printouts; photographs / Support: paper; photographic paper
    Note: Press release, photograph, and clippings of international conference Education for Landscape Planning. Includes conference schedule and list of people invited to make presentations. Organized by Carl Steinitz, his welcome remarks are included, as are brief outlines of speakers.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1981-1984; 1999; Folder: DC017; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 10-1/2" x 6" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Programs of commencement ceremonies: Commencement Ceremony, 1983, Commencement Ceremony, 1981, and Order of Exercises for Commencement, 1984.
    Note: Also includes poster for conference entitled Exploring (New) Urbanism.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1995; Folder: DC018; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 10-1/2" x 6" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Programs of commencement ceremonies: Commencement Ceremony, 1995, and Commencement Week Program, 1995.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1958-1987; Folder: DC019; / Quantity: 24 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 8-1/2" x 6"; 9-1/2" x 7-1/2"; 16" x 20"; 4" x 12" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Miscellaneous brochures, leaflets and cards for lectures and exhibitions. Includes text of 11th Annual Gropius Lecture by Barbara Ward (on occasion of the dedication of Gund Hall, and entitled An Urban Planet. Also included are brochures and/or cards for "Prudential Center Revisited", "Irvine by Design", "Olmsted the Man and the Artist", "Last Fifty Years of Italian Architecture Reflected in the Eyes of an Architect", "Democratic Theory and Urban Form", "Four Public Squares for Leonforte". Included as well are announcements for Gropius Lectures ("Constancy, Time and Architecture" and "Architecture Without Frontiers"), Dan Kiley Lectures, and Kenzo Tange Lecture.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1976-1980; Folder: DC020; / Quantity: 10 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 9" x 4"; 17" x 17"; 24" x 30"; 4" x 7-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Materials related to the 75th anniversary of the Landscape Architecture Department.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1982-1986; Folder: DC021; / Quantity: 11 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 9" x 4" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Miscellaneous brochures about special programs within the GSD: Program in Advanced Environmental Studies, Community Assistance Program. Also includes fact sheets and brochures by and about the Graduate School of Design. Also included is Bill Saunder's article "Architectural Education: Current Confusions - is Architecture Allegory, Craft, or Art", published in Architectural Record, May 1986. Special Programs also include the Loeb Fellowship Program, Career Discovery, and Continuing Education.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1974-1989; Folder: DC022; / Quantity: 15 items / Dimensions: 18" x 18"; 23" x 18"; 8" x 4"; 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print; typescript / Support: paper
    Note: File includes brochures, posters and leaflets of conferences and lectures. Included are "German Werkbund: The Pleasures of Form and the Realities of Life" (1980 Gropius Lecture); "Professions and the Built Environment"; "Between Art and Industry: The Deutscher Werkbund"; "Between Art and Industry: The Deutscher Werkbund"; "Thinking the Present"; "Urban Architecture: The Park Square Sketch Problem"; "Growth Management for Cities and Towns: The Role of Elected and Appointed Officials"; and "Second International Conference on Urban Design".
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1974; Folder: DC023; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 9" x 4"; 6" x 8-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Brochures for the following conferences: "The Professions and the Built Environment" and "The Future Role of Professionals in the Built Environment". The latter includes texts of Gropius Lecture (by Serge Chermayeff), Opening Address (by Alan Altshuler), and Closing Paper (by Gerald McCue).
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1990; Folder: DC024; / Quantity: 4 items / Dimensions: 9-1/2" x 7-1/2"; 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print; typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Notes from Richardson / Corbu Celebration Committee final meeting and brochure prepared for the celebration of birthdays.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1989; Folder: DC025; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 10" x 7-1/2" / Medium: print; typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Posters for the Richardson Celebration (151st Birthday of H. H. Richardson and Recognition of the Urban Environment of Copley Square).
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1992; Folder: DC026; / Quantity: 6 items / Dimensions: 17" x 8-1/2"; 8" x 10" / Medium: print; photographs / Support: paper; photographic paper
    Note: Dean's Day brochure and photographs, 1992. (Dean at the time: Peter Rowe). Speakers: Michael Hays, Richard Forman, Alan Altshuler, Alex Krieger, and Jorge Silvetti.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1995; Folder: DC027; / Quantity: 41 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 5" x 7"; 1-1/2" x 6" / Medium: photographs; contacts / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Photographs and contacts of Boston Bash, 27 October 1995 at Harvard Club of Boston.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1993; Folder: DC028; / Quantity: 9 items / Dimensions: 5" x 7"; 5" x 8-1/2"; 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: photographs; typescripts / Support: photographic paper; paper
    Note: Brochure, schedule and photographs of conference The Environment, Sustainable Development and Design.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): ca. 1965; Folder: DC029; / Quantity: 1 item / Medium: photographs; typescripts / Support: photographic paper; paper
    Note: Magnetic tape of Sasaki Landscape Architecture Jury, ca. 1965 (3rd year jury).
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1994; Folder: DC030; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescripts / Support: paper
    Note: Transcripts of conference and publication proposal for Denaturalized Urbanity, organized by Mohsen Mostafavi, 1994. Includes abstracts and draft texts.
    Local Note: This item is restricted. For consultation only, no reproductions, nor citations allowed in some cases (by request of the authors).
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1995-2003; Folder: DC031; / Quantity: 26 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 8" x 10" / Medium: typescripts; photographs; negatives / Support: paper; photographic paper
    Note: Records relative two initiatives by the Advances Studies Program students: Testing Ground and Discipline Problems. Also includes photographs, proofs for covers for the journal Assemblage.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1997; Folder: DC032; / Quantity: 77 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescripts; printouts / Support: paper
    Note: From folder labeled "Harry Seidler". Includes materials related to The Hudnut / Gropius Years Event at the GSD, 1997 (program, speakers, registration forms, so forth). Includes printout of talk by Harry Seidler (The Gropius Years), Sam Hurst (Revelation, Reason and Reaction: A Memoir on Gropius and the Bauhaus).
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1975; Folder: DC033; / Quantity: 18 items / Dimensions: 8" x 10"; 3" x 5" / Medium: photographs / Support: paper
    Note: Photographs from the 1975 Anniversary Celebration of the first 75 years of the Department of Landscape Architecture. Assembled and identified by Carl Steinitz.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1945-1946; Folder: DC034; / Quantity: 3 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: copies / Support: paper
    Note: From Harry Seidler, outline / description of a sketch problem in Gropius' class of 1945-1946. Includes copies of drawings for a House in Belmont.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1999; Folder: DC035; / Quantity: 19 items / Dimensions: 5" x 7"; 8" x 10" / Medium: photographs; contacts / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Photographs of New Urbanism Conference. Many include Andres Duany, Alek Krieger, and Rem Koolhaas.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1995; Folder: DC036; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: photographs; contacts / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Memorandum from Alex Krieger to speakers at the Boston Bash Panel related to the themes of the discussion.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1995; Folder: DC037; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 16" x 11-1/2" / Medium: newsprint / Support: paper
    Note: Issue of Harvard University Gazette that includes a section on "Harvard Builds Boston", photographs include buildings (Hancock Tower) and people (Bill Saunders, Robert Campbell, Peter Rowe).
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 1986-1993; Folder: DC038; / Quantity: 15 items / Dimensions: 16" x 11-1/2" / Medium: typescript; print / Support: paper
    Note: File includes brochures, posters, and written materials in relation to a series of exhibitions and conferences. Included are: Ethics and the Practice of Architecture, Central Artery Tunnel, Memory Games (Peter Eisenman); Stereotomic Permutations (Preston Scott Cohen), Hugh Stubbins and His Associates: The First Fifty Years, 70s: The Formation of Contemporary Architectural Discourse (the latter a joint conference between GSD and Cornell University.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 2000; Folder: DC039; / Quantity: 1 items / Dimensions: 11" x 11" / Medium: dye / Support: cotton
    Note: File includes t-shirt distributed at the GSD on occassion of the Comme des Garcons exhibition, 2000. Cotton, shrink-wrapped in plastic; blue and black typography on white background.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 2005; Folder: DC040; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: contact prints / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Contact sheets with photographs of the Veronika Rudge Green Award in Urban Design ceremony, 2005. Prize awarded to the City of Aleppo, Syria.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 2006; Folder: DC041; / Quantity: 21 items / Dimensions: 5" x 7" / Medium: photographs / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Round table held at GSD to celebrate Henry Cobb's 80th birthday. Round table consisted of former and current GSD Deans and Heads of the Architecture Department. Among them: Harry Cobb, Toshiko Mori, Jorge Silvetti, Gerald McCue, Mack Scogin, and Rafael Moneo. Also present Michael Hays, Peter Eisenman and Jeffrey Kipnis.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 2002; Folder: DC042; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 5" x 7" x 1" / Medium: VHS video
    Note: VHS video of Women in Design Panel, held at the GSD in 2002.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 2000; Folder: DC043; / Quantity: 7 items / Dimensions: 12" x 10" x 2" / Medium: print; photographic print / Support: paper
    Note: Brown party bag with items given out at Jorge Silvetti's 25th Anniversary of his association with the GSD. Celebration held in New York City. Includes issue of Gamut, Robert Wilson's booklet on the 1997 Excellence in Design Award, and two "masks" with photograph Professor Silvetti's face. Also included is an issue of Unprecedented Realism.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 2000; Folder: DC044; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 15" x 13"; 2" x 2" x 2" / Support: cotton; plexiglass
    Note: File includes a cotton bag and a plexi paperweight that read: "One Hundred Years of Landscape Architecture at Harvard, 1900-2000." Given as gifts for the anniversary of the Landscape Architecture Department.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 2000; Folder: DC045; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 9" x 12" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: File includes crimson 9" x 12" folder with agenda, program and cards given out to attendees at the symposium for the 100th Year Anniversary of Landscape Architecture at Harvard.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 2000; Folder: DC046; / Quantity: 8 items / Dimensions: 5" x 6-1/2"; 4" x 5" / Medium: negatives; print / Support: acetate; paper
    Note: Invitations and negatives related to the Landscape Architecture Department's 100th Year Anniversary, held at the GSD in 2000. Invitations include cards for a gala dinner and another for a dinner in honor of Hideo Sasaki (and recipient of the Centennial Award). Both in April, 2000.
    Note: Also included is a card announcing lecture by Edward O. Wilson on "The Biological Basis of Landscape Design."
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 2000; Folder: DC047; / Quantity: 23 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: photostats / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Photostats of articles on landscape and photostats covers of landscape publications. Most probably used for the exhibit at One Hundred Years of Landscape Architecture at Harvard held at the GSD in 2000.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 2000; Folder: DC048; / Quantity: 3 items / Dimensions: 8" x 10" / Medium: mounted photographs / Support: photographic paper; foamcore
    Note: Mounted photographs: Sandy Calder with student at Robinson Hall, landscape studio class at Robinson Hall, late-20th century class of landscape architecture GSD graduates. Most probably used for the exhibit at One Hundred Years of Landscape Architecture at Harvard held at the GSD in 2000.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 2000; Folder: DC049; / Quantity: 13 items / Dimensions: 5" x 7" / Medium: mounted photographs / Support: photographic paper; foamcore
    Note: Mounted photographs of landscape-related people, events, classes and projects. Most probably used for the exhibit at One Hundred Years of Landscape Architecture at Harvard held at the GSD in 2000.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 2000; Folder: DC050; / Quantity: 19 items / Dimensions: 8" x 8" / Medium: mounted photographs / Support: photographic paper; foamcore
    Note: Mounted photographs, portraits of people related to the landscape architecture department at Harvard. Most probably used for the exhibit at One Hundred Years of Landscape Architecture at Harvard held at the GSD in 2000.
    Note: Portraits of Peter Walker, Gerald McCue, Charles Eliot, Joseph Hudnut, Maurice Kilbridge, James Sturgis Pray, Bremmer Whidden Pond, Peter Rowe, George Hargreaves, Hideo Sasaki, Frederick Law Olmsted Jr., Charles W. Harris, Laurie Olin, Linda Jewell, Norman Newton, Lester Collins, Michael van Valkenburgh, Carl Steinitz, Josep Lluis Sert.
  - Subseries DC: Events -- Conferences, Lectures, and Symposia, / Date(s): 2000; Folder: DC051; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 11" x 14" / Medium: mounted photographs / Support: photographic paper; foamcore
    Note: Mounted photographs of a graduating class (n.d.) in front of Robinson Hall. Most probably used for the exhibit at One Hundred Years of Landscape Architecture at Harvard held at the GSD in 2000.